

About me

As a highly motivated and committed web developer and graduate Engineer for Electrical Engineering and Telecommunication, you will get with me:

- Work experience in various technical fields
- Compliance with high quality standards
- On-time project delivery
- IT-driven curiosity

Out of passion for digital technology and trends, I switched my career path to programming in 2019. In order to generate more know-how, I successfully completed a full-stack Web development course based on the MERN stack at DCI. I look forward to providing you with my knowledge and analytical skills in Web development.

## Skills

### Technologies: JavaScript Frameworks:

• React Native

Bootstrap

• React / Redux

- JavaScript
- HTML5
- CSS3
- Node.js
- CMS
- Databases:

#### Version Control:

- MongoDB
- Mongoose
- MySQL
- Git

Vue

jQuery

Angular

- GitHub
- GitLab

## Languages

English (C1) German (B2) Serbian Croatian

## Contact

- Frankfurt am Main
- +49 174 623 15 25
- ☑ alen.eftimov@gmail.com
- https://github.com/Alen-Eftimov
- in www.linkedin.com/in/eftimov-alen
- https://www.xing.com/profile /Alen\_Eftimov3/cv

# **Alen Eftimov**

## Full Stack Web Developer

### Education

2019 - 2021

DCI Hamburg – DigitalCareerInstitute gGmbH

Full Stack Web Developer

Successful completion of a one-year training course based on MERN Stack, including several practical project works

1995 - 2006

Faculty of Electronic Engineering Niš - University of Niš, Serbia M.Sc. in Electrical and Telecommunications Engineering

## Experience

06/2022 11/2021

Site-Works - Frankfurt am Main

Web Developer - Freelancer:

- On the satisfaction clients I updated websites for Tefal, Sander Group, KRUPS, Clean FFM, T21, Gerbermühle, 1250Nieder Eschbach, with the following technologies: Java Script, HTML5, CSS3, CMS (Grav, WordPress, Contao), PHP/Symfony, GitHub, GitLab.
- As well, I worked on the development of a mobile application, for providing Taxi services and I used technologies: React Native, JavaScript, CSS3 and Android Studio.

Independent Designer Engineer of Telecommunications systems -2014 - 2017 Belgrade, Serbia

- Designing: Video surveillance, Alarm systems, Fire alarms, Sound systems, Computer, Telephone and Optical networks.
- Technologies used: AutoCad, MS Office

2013 - 2014 CEG International - Doha, Qatar

Supervisor / Consultant for Telecommunications systems:

Supervision - Work on Telecommunications systems projects.

2007 - 2013

ARHIPRO - Belgrade, Serbia

Designer Engineer for Telecommunications systems:

• Work on Telecommunications systems projects.

## Relevant Projects

**Dr.House -** https://dr-house.herokuapp.com

- Multi-purpose health care website for hospitals, clinics, doctors and patients with a focus on CRUD admin page.
- Technologies used: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, NodeJS, EJS, Bootstrap, MongoDB

**WebShopReactApp -** https://web-shop-app-react.netlify.app

- Frontend eCommerce application based on React.
- Technologies used: React, React Hooks, React Router, ES6, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, Material UI.
- portfolioAlen https://alen-eftimov-portfolio.herokuapp.com

## **Expertise**

Web development Responsive design

Clean Coding

### **Hobbies & Interests**



Database systems